tnawrestlingnews.com 2011-12-31

# TNA Wrestling News & Rumors, TNA News - TNAWrestlingNews.com

## Privacy Statement:

### TNAWrestlingNews.com Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

#### 

TNAWrestlingNews.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: TNAWrestlingNews.com 

#### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

#### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.

#### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

#### Contests

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. TNAWrestlingNews.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Data Quality/Access

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: You can send email to [TNA Wrestling News Staff.](mailto:tnawrestlingnews@yahoo.com)

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [TNA Wrestling News Staff.](mailto:tnawrestlingnews@yahoo.com)

This page has been viewed times.
